







•

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

## Summary

Jump to Section

B.Tech Graduate from Delhi Technological University (formerly DCE) Professional with skills in Business Analytics, Research, Web Development, Project Management, Machine Learning, JavaScript, MongoDB, Tableau, Python, MySQL, HTML, CSS, PHP, AWS, C, C++, Research.

# **Work Experience**

Vida Salvateur International Pvt. Ltd. as Research Intern lug 2019 to July 2019

Jun 2019 to Jul 2019

Worked with marketing team of 30 people, gained insight of IoT (Internet of things) based Solution.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

National Institute of Electronics & Information Technology as Trainee Jun 2019 to Aug 2019

Training in VLSI and created simulated traffic light controller

EazyPG Startup as Management Trainee Feb 2019 to Aug 2019

Worked Under Guidance of Team Leader with team size of 30 people, gave 20% more profitable consumer base in North Delhi

Ministry of Road Transport & Highways (Govt. of India) as Research & Analysis Dec 2017 to Apr 2018

Analyzed accident prone zones in Delhi. Implemented solution that resulted in decreasing no. of accidents/day from 3 to 0.

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Delhi College of Engineering (DCE), Delhi in 2020

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Python Advertising & Society Excel for Business

Excel Skills for Business: Essentials

### **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
(Python,C++,R) HTML, CSS		
JavaScript, PHP, AWS, PowerBI		
MySQL, MongoDB, Excel, Tableau		
Word, Machine Learning, Web Technologies		
Advanced Excel	0	0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

### **Projects**

Project Title: Covid-19 Analysis Client: SELF WORK

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: May 2020 - Jul 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Analyzed Covid-19 using R, Python.

Also Made real time Covid-19 data fetching python program using web scrapper API

Project Title: Video Chatting Client: Self Practice

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Apr 2020 - Jun 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Learned and Created Group video chatting Web App using API.

Project Title: Python Projects

Client: Self Practice

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Mar 2020 - May 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Mini projects like Auto Reply for WhatsApp, Audiobooks using Python

Project Title: Portfolio Website

Client: SELF WORK

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Nov 2019 - Jan 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Made portfolio website of my works & skills: www.tenbyzero.in

Used latest technologies to built it like MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js)

Project Title: Snake Robot

Client: DTU

Duration: May 2019 - Jun 2020 Nature of Employment: Full Time Role: Project Leader Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 3

Skill Used: Market Research, Software, Design Engineering, Python

Role Description: Made initial frameworks Designed the robot in Autodesk software. Presented the ideas to Professors

Project Details: Designed & simulated Snake like Robot in Autodesk fusion using Vrep. Added Serpentine motions,

especially designed for military purposes

^ Back to Top

### **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.